[{
        "question": "84 ÷ 4",
        "answer": "21",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "90 ÷ 9",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "72 ÷ 8",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "45 ÷ 5",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "56 ÷ 7",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "96 ÷ 6",
        "answer": "16",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "63 ÷ 9",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "81 ÷ 9",
        "answer": "9",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "64 ÷ 8",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "88 ÷ 11",
        "answer": "8",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "120 ÷ 10",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "144 ÷ 12",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "98 ÷ 7",
        "answer": "14",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "150 ÷ 15",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "108 ÷ 9",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "60 ÷ 6",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "70 ÷ 10",
        "answer": "7",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "80 ÷ 8",
        "answer": "10",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "132 ÷ 11",
        "answer": "12",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    },
    {
        "question": "110 ÷ 10",
        "answer": "11",
        "qType": "text",
        "aType": "text"
    }
]